glodnews.com 2018-04-20

# Privacy Policy - Travel News, Tips, and Guides Travel News, Tips, and Guides

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is paramount and we do not sell our database (information about you) to any other party.

All definitions shall be construed the same as the ones contained within the Terms of Use.

The Travel Magazine is committed to ensuring that Your privacy is protected. This privacy policy explains how We use the information We collect about You, how You can instruct Us if You prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that We have in place to safeguard Your privacy.

1\. The information collected and how We use it

When You write to Us, We need to know Your name and e-mail address (or as required).

We gather this information to allow Us to process Your inquiry. The relevant information is then used by Us, our agents and sub-contractors to communicate with You on any matter relating to your inquiry and the provision of the Service in general.

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help Us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.

From time to time We may use Your information for research and analysis purposes so that We can monitor and improve the Service We provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact You by e-mail to ask You for Your feedback and comments on our service.

We may also wish to provide You with information about special features of our website or any other service or products We think may be of interest to You. If You would not like to receive this information, please contact us.

We may also want to provide You with related information from third parties We think may be of interest to You. If You would like to receive this information, please contact us.

We may also provide Your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services We believe may be of interest to You. If You wish Us to disclose Your information in this way, please contact us.

2\. Our use of cookies and other information gathering technologies

Our website creates a single cookie on your machine containing session and state information. This is a unique digital identity for each person visiting the site. Cookies cannot be used by themselves by a third party to identify you.

The information within this cookie does not include personal or financial information. Our website requires cookies to be allowed in your browser to permit creation and to allow features and actions on the site to work without restriction.

Cookies may also be installed on your machine by the advertisers featured on The Travel Magazine. These cookies are generally used purely for the purposes of monitoring the number of times an ad has been seen and clicked on.

3\. How We protect Your information

The internet is not a secure medium. However We have put in place various security procedures.

Any personal information stored in our database is only accessible by The Company staff through a password protected interface. The database itself is hosted by HawkHost.com, who have their own internal security procedures to protect the database from unauthorised access.

We also keep Your information confidential. Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of Your information.

4\. Sale of business

If this business is sold or integrated with another business Your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

5\. Updating Your details

If any of the information that You have provided to Us changes, for example if You change Your e-mail address, name or if You wish to cancel Your registration, please let Us know the correct details by contacting us.

6\. Your consent

By submitting Your information You consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If We change our Privacy Policy We will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that You may be aware of the information We collect and how We use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that You agree to any such changes.

7\. How to contact Us

We welcome Your views about our website and our privacy policy. If You would like to contact Us with any queries or comments please click here.

Contact Information  
Please use our “Contact” page to direct any concerns or questions about this privacy policy.
